foreign
distortions
and unfortunately most people take the
10 Distortion and make it production of
the church
so uh
we have the Quran as the Cotillion to
correct any devious
from Genesis 6
11.
it says in the eyes of God the Earth was
corrupt and full of lawlessness
when God saw how corrupt the Earth had
become
since all mountains
let the framed lights on Earth he said
to Noah
I have decided to put an end to all
Mortals on Earth
the Earth is full of lawlessness because
of them so I will destroy them and all
life on Earth
make yourself an art
so the idea
is
when there is too much lawlessness on
Earth Disobedience of God
and not adherence to the Oneness of God
God the story of Earth and I want to use
this to
point out to you
that you
probably saved the Earth
you
because you are people who believe in
God alone
you do not idolize Muhammad or Jesus or
Mary or anything or anyone or anything
you because
you have reached the convictions of God
Alone is King
and God Alone rules the world and rules
your life every minute detail in it
nobody controls your life you have come
to this conviction you know that your
boss has no Authority on you
God
controls the minds and hearts of
everybody including the people around
you your boss your spouse your children
your parents
everybody you've come to that conclusion
food back in 1977
it will start the master 77 or 78 you
know
78.
this mask was established because
we came to the conclusion that Quran
like God says is the only source
this is why this mask started but before
that we want to look together on the
earth now God look at the Earth in
Noah's time and he said nobody believes
in God alone and there is too much
lawlessness so I'm gonna destroy the
Earth and I wipe out everyone
that's what God Said
we have it in the Quran and we have it
in the Bible
now of all the millions of Christians
you see on Earth
how many
believe in God alone
how many believe that Jesus is a human
being who has no power to do anything a
helpless
dead person how many of the Christians
believe that
and I worship God Alone
of all the Millions
of all the millions of Muslims on Earth
how many believe God when he says Quran
alone
how many how many masks on Earth
without any other names
in the other end
how many none
you very probably saved the Earth
because everybody was corrupt how many
Jews
adhere to the book of God Alone
and do not follow Hadith and Sunnah
how many
none they all follow Hadith they don't
follow the Torah
exactly the world Hadith in their
language is called the mishnah which
means aura or Hadith
and gemara which means Traditions or
soon
these are the people who believe in God
and they were all corrupt they are all
corrupt
probably was a blessing from God that I
worked for the United Nations and
travels in every Muslim country
and everywhere I dug up
the most religious of every country and
having seen one place that was not
praise and worship Muhammad day or night
instead of God or beside God I mean they
worshiped God
and they pray the five prayers exactly
to God but they insert
names of Muhammad and Ibrahim in their
prayer
I haven't seen one place
on Earth that worships God Alone
when
corruption takes over the Earth
there's no need for the earth to exist
the end of the world will come because
there will be no one who worships God
Alone
but it has been in God's knowledge and
predestination that the mosque of Tucson
will come to be
the people who worship God Alone
this is the only mosque on Earth that
says
without any other names
by the way we had three people here you
saw me discuss things with them and they
were angry because in our Adam
who said I said well guess what guess
why they were angry can anybody make a
guess
most of the
yeah because they didn't say Muhammad
you're wrong
no because you wouldn't mention the name
of Ali
it happened to be Shiites
we don't say
it's his Idol you know
so I mean what did you like our other
and I was just like Fatima I thought
yeah well when you mentioned the name of
Allah alone
but uh they went on to uh indicate it
was because Ali's name was not there
but this is the only mosque in the world
that mentioned the name of Allah I don't
want to worship Allah and that was it I
enjoying today
and on every spot on earth
there isn't any that has only the name
of God
and when corruption
spreads in this way God destroys the
Earth
I want you to look at in the Quran at
Surah 30 verse 41
foreign
verse 41 says
corruption has prevailed throughout the
land and see you to the people's work
in my new translation I'm going to have
this misery instead of corruption misery
therefore he makes Them Suffer Well it's
self-explanatory he makes them suffer
the consequences of their words
that they may return
it's very very possible that you
saved
you hear what's happening what's
happening in California
you can see what happened to Malibu
Beach
all those Mansions turned into sticks
this is God God is angry at California
this is California from border to border
from Mexico to Oregon
it's being slammed hit
unbelievable the pictures that you saw
just it is believable of course God is
angry at California
as we see in the Bible in the Quran and
God's law never changes
back in 1977 there was no one on earth
that I know anyway
the voice of God Alone they always have
Idols beside him
you look at the Christians the Jews the
Muslims
and it is an unfortunate fact of life
what you want to show you in this life
it's the statement in the Quran
which is the majority of people
no matter what you do will not believe
I'm not with you
and this statement here says the
Believers the majority of people will
not even believe in God and then you
take the minority that is the Believers
and God says a statement of fact that is
assured by two other negatives
that the majority of the minority
the majority of the Believers are Idol
worshipers
they worship God but they also idolize
Muhammad or Jesus or Mary or somebody or
something
they just cannot come all the way
those fingers alone
so if you are with the majority of a
deep trouble
even if you are with the with the
majority of the minority
if you are with the minority of
believers
you have to find out are you and the
majority of this minority or are you in
the minority of the minority
your Elite of the elite
and it's very difficult
problem is these people who are
believers but they fell into either
worship they sent their righteous
they sincerely think they are righteous
as you see up here they think that they
are rightly guided
they think that they are right they died
you think they are actually going
repeated in the Quran
and here we this is a verse that you're
familiar with on the day of judgment
where they say by God our Lord we were
not either worshipers
on the day of the ultimate face to face
with Allah
and they swear
but they were not either worshipers
if you still have the same page
41.
I'm gonna go on to 42 the sketch two
seven eight
say travel the Earth and see the
consequences for those before you or
look up California not the world the
majority of them were either worshipers
therefore you shall devote yourself to
that perfect religion before a day comes
that is inevitable
on that day the people will be stunned
however this believes causes its own
detriment
and those who are righteousness do so
for their own good
God bestows his grace upon upon those
who believe in all righteousness who are
those who disbelieve are displeasing him
foreign
because as you see you are a very small
minority of the minority
you're a very special person when you
come to that
um Satan will concentrate all his forces
on you
you does not want you to make it because
when you make it making it means kinship
on Earth sovereignty on Earth and
rolling all your surroundings perfect
happiness in this world as in the Hera
and that's nothing easy
I mean to qualify for a job you go to
the university and work your head off
for four years
to qualify for a job so to qualify for
kingship on Earth what do you expect
it's very difficult
and this is why
let's look at 29 2. 29
H270
Alm do the people think they would be
enough to say we believe without being
put to the test
we have tested the generations before
them for God must distinguish those who
are truthful from those who are liars
you you cannot be enough you will not be
left alone to say I believe you have to
be put to the test and it is a severe
test
because there is too much at stake
this kingship on Earth at stake this
perfect happiness
so you would have to be put to the test
because God wants
to show you to the angels
and to tell them look at my creature
under any circumstances he believes in
me look at Surah 12.
yeah 40 38 let's start at 38 so at 12.
38.
that's one five eight
this is Joseph speaking
I follow the religion of my father's
Abraham Isaac and Jacob we never worship
anything beside God
this is what Grace comes out upon us and
upon the people but most people are not
appreciative
now uh let's go on 39th all my prison
companions
is it better to have several Idols or
one card the most powerful
you only idolize beside God Idols that
you may come you and your parents God
never places any power in them
kingship belongs only to God he
commanded that you shall not worship
except to him this is the perfect
religion but most people do not know now
here is Joseph preaching one God and
worshiping one God and where is he
in prison
he's a prophet of God in prison
because God wants to show
the angels and Satan
that look at myself and Joseph look at
my creature Joseph
it doesn't matter what condition he's in
he knows I am the king and he worships
me alone
look at uh
42.
he then said to if I want to be said
remember me at your lord The King
but the devil made him forget to
remember him at his goal and Joseph
remained in prison a few more years
a prophet of God Joseph who preaches the
one God
and just like that a few more years in
prison some people come to me and say
I've been a Muslim two weeks why am I
having all these problems
patience
you have to have patience
it is Joseph in prison
and the man who was supposed to save him
he forgot so Joseph stays in prison a
few more years
but listen your guaranteed kingship on
Earth
let us go on
tonight verse 19 same Surah of Joseph
what does 90 say
page 162 they said you must be Joseph
it's his brothers he said I am Joseph
and this is my brother God has been
gracious to us if anyone Works
righteousness and steadfastly perseveres
this is required rotations steadfastness
perseverance
you can't come to Islam six months and
then demand kingship on Earth
you must steadfastly persevere
you must prove
that you really believe under any
circumstance you have to be put to the
test
but you are in God's eyes throughout the
test he may push you to the brink but he
will always watch over you you will
never fall
because if you fall he'll hold you back
but you will be on the brink because God
wants to be proud of you and he wants to
tell Satan and the engines look at my
creature it doesn't matter what
conditions he's in now look at 110 of
the Same Soul
that's one six four
just as The Messengers reached the point
of Despair and imagine that they have
failed our Victory comes to them we then
save whomever we will while the guilty
can never evade our retribution so when
you reach the point of despair
you're a believer in God alone
nothing changes your conviction
then comes kingship on Earth Joseph was
a king on Earth and he was controlling
the provisions for the whole Middle East
his brothers came from Palestine all the
way to Egypt to beg for grain
and he was giving them
a common Lord per person he decided that
he was in good control of them he was a
king on Earth his brother and his
parents they fed trust me before him
he became this is this is what is
guaranteed to you
but you have to steadfastly for severe
you have to prove yourself
what happens in the test
that's an agreement that God has with
Satan
he says you go and do anything you want
and if you contact them they're yours
now we are Satan's our most Ardent enemy
and when you come to that he will come
and tempt you with your most
urgent needs
to read money he will tempt you with
money
if you need sex you will tempt you with
sex you need whatever is your most
urgent need he will tempt you with that
to take you away from that number
and if you fall this bed is delicious
and Powerful
debate for the fish must be the best you
go on you when you go fishing you pick
out the best bait salmon eggs
we'll just find something better words
the bed must be fantastic for the fish
but as soon as you catch the fish what
do you do to it you cut its head and you
pry it the noise you take a test
intestines out
that's what certain will do to you
once once he has you because he's our
enemy
so the test
is very powerful
this is why the job said the following
in Surah 38 look at Surah 38 verse 41.
38 41 the top of pitch three one two
recall our servant job he called his
Lord saying the devil has Afflicted me
with disease and suffered so it's not
God who really affects them you see what
happened as we learned from the story of
job is that God was proud of job
and he was telling the angels and Satan
look at myself and Joe he worships me
alone
you know they're very rare people the
people who worship God Alone are very
rare
and God was proud of job at the time and
he was telling the angels look at my
servant show
and sit and said well look at him he is
Rich he has a family he's
he he's not under any pressure so why
shouldn't he worship you
and God said okay I'm gonna lent you a
job for a while now remember job is
always in God's eye and Satan has limits
where he can go
so certain
started to work on Zone
and this is why you see recall our
servants oh he called his Lord saying
the devil has Afflicted me with disease
and suffering
he knows okay job knows
and so
God May Dent you to Satan for Hawaii and
if Satan can take you you're his just
like when you catch a fish
it's gonna fraud you
and when you flank a test you regress
you start again at square one square
zero
so we have to turn to God right now and
do two things first thank him
for saving the planet Earth because of
us
thank you for guiding us
whatever let our steps to this place
me and you
this is the greatest blessing that ever
happened to you and we have to thank God
for it then we're going to ask God to
keep us on the path steadfastly
persevere no matter what happens
steadfasty perseverance nothing will
take us away
foreign
situations in the Hereafter actual
situations in the hereafter
and the in my last hope I talked to you
about the verse that you saw here where
God gathers people and asked them what
are the idols to help you and they say
by God our Lord we were not either
worshipers
it's an actual situation where people
are not aware now they'll swear to you
they are not idle worshipers and their
swear then under the day of judgment
that they were not they are not either
worshipers they are not aware
and I went through the science
of idol worship that they cannot stand
to talk about Allah alone
they cannot follow the Quran alone 1745
and they cannot accept What God Says in
the Quran
the translation for you incredible
wasn't it
they changed his uh
straying into a virtue that he was lost
in love for people for his people
whatever that crazy translation was and
I will continue that situation of actual
situations in the hereafter
uh
and and this was in the next next photo
this is a human being
this is this was a human being
someday it's going to look like this
just imagine a handsome Abdullah it's
gonna look like this someday
[Music]
beautiful rahima would look like this
someday
for some people like myself this is an
improvement
this person had beautiful teeth
braces and this is the person that lived
on earth just like we are now
and you can imagine how many times
we just was eating
and this happens to be a girl
and she can you imagine how many times
she chew and shoot food
you can look you can see the tea is how
much
the food affected her teeth
she she probably worked
she had the boss
she had lots of food
to drove a car maybe
she had fights
with her friends relatives she yelled at
them
she made love
she
I don't know how many miles she walked
this was a person you're gonna be like
this your body will be like this
now I want to uh
draw your attention to God's design
imagine God designing the human the
skull just the skull
imagine
just for the sake of
understanding imagine God like a big
architect chairman of the board and a
big desk
and designing the human skull
and God says I'm going to leave two
openings for the eyes because this human
being would have two eyes
and we have to have an opening in here
for the air to breathe
now
the eyeballs will go in this in this
home so God says I'm going to have this
eye sockets
and if you look in there you see very
tiny holes inside for the nerve the
optic nerve that goes to go to the brain
and
we're gonna have if you look in here and
you see the sinus
passages
and the teeth is something that the
design of the teeth and the Cutters and
the shoulders
foreign
leads to a
the audio nerve go to the brain and this
is very hard you know very to protect
the brain then put the brain inside
let's see this opens
now God didn't put these things on the
spring nobody else did that
my goodness see this is very tough It's
Made of a number of layers you can see
the layers there
this was a human being look what we're
doing with her
the brand was as protected and fluid
because it's very important
and then see the opening at the bottom
of the skull
this goes to the spine
everything all the the word is
controlled this way
now I want to move on to a situation in
the hill
this person
this was the Garment
this person was worried
but the person herself
is asleep just
she doesn't know that she died
Resurrection
whether this person
let us say she's an average Christian or
an average Muslim for that matter on
average Joe
who fell into Idol Washington
so she would get up
to rise there
Resurrection all the people on earth
who existed on Earth
will be up on this Earth
Resurrected
and this person would say
oh God it's true
whoa
everything we heard is true there's
really Resurrection
I didn't pay attention to this day
and look at that big person over there
see they should have a small size
but the body's in here after
and she'll go to this big person and she
said I'll take a look
and he'll say well for one thing
I never missed breakfast
defensive Trail
and she would say I didn't miss
breakfast either
you know eggs and
bread
and the other thing I would say
yeah but you were feeding your garment
you know how's my acting by the way
I'm bad
I should have also The Voice
whoa
just don't call Hollywood I'm happy in
my position
I don't want the directors bugging me
but this is an actual situation where
people would be in different different
sizes
and then she would ask what is going to
happen now
you would say what
the next thing that would happen is God
will come
for this Earth
and the energy associated with God is
equivalent to millions of hydrogen bonds
can you imagine this Earth a million
hydrogen bombs falling on it
what will happen see this is why that
took us nuclear science
is why God God let us invent
hydrogen bomb so we can't understand
what happens when he comes this is what
the Quran says
and
that big person will go on and say when
God comes you can't stand it first of
all the energy associated with God is
equivalent to millions of hydrogen bonds
and when God comes this whole earth is
going to shatter into pieces
the chameleon hydrogen bombs head on
them
the Stars would crash
and just integrate
and you are going to be in bad trouble
you cannot stand the presence of God
so she will say what will you do
you say I'm gonna feed on that energy
I'm going to enjoy it immensely
and as soon as God comes we're going to
be stratified
into ranks
you would have to run away
to help
this will be actual conversations
and she will say well I'm going to run
to Jesus and see if he can hit me
because I
I believed in Jesus
and she may go to Jesus and he'll say
I didn't get to all of Myself by helping
you know we're all in heaven right now
is there any service Resurrection is in
him
I can't help you
God is the one who created you God is
the one who provided for you God is the
one who terminated your life God is the
one who resurrected you and God is the
one
who will hold you to account according
to account
if this person were a Muslim should say
I'm gonna run to Muhammad he is my safia
he's my intercessor
foreign
that day is going to come see this
person left here on Earth
and she did everything you are doing now
and you're going to be like this person
someday
100 years from now
you may not look this good by the way
this looks very good
she didn't have this for tea
so we must
in order to stay on the path you must
stay you must remember
those actual situations that will be
here and this is why God puts belief in
the Hereafter next to him
they're both required you cannot make it
you can believe in God and still go to
hell you saw the slide
the majority of people who believe in
God according to him you must believe in
God and in the hereafter
you must never neglect to feed your soul
because this is what the body will look
like and people like myself will stand
around with it you know she didn't know
that this
somebody they claimed with my strong
someday you know I don't care it's a
garment that they throw away
remember your old clothes to give away
do you care who's doing what with them
now
your body is just like that
all close
all garments
so
you neglect to feel yourself it's your
own fault
the five fails each day those are the
five minutes
the five players are useless if you
idolize anyone else the son of God
must be the only one not number one
because number one means there is number
two
God must be the only one in your life
with 100 seats here
God multiplies the rewards many forms
for whatever he works
God is
so this is the
simple spirit is the minimum reward for
charitable
access
well every dollar is spent you get 700.
foreign
what we're seeing here is the ethical
strategy
a lot of people may give assistance to
somebody and then
hurt their feelings later on
without this city saying the world
never forget
together
and the God says
this is
mostly spend their monies in the code of
God and do not follow their charity with
their approach or else
you receive the recompense them before
they agree and another verse if they
don't remember exactly word now
since it is the next one 263.
describe words of compassion are better
than alternative which is
better for being a kind of professional
to help someone and then
never forget
something
the idea is that the money that you have
is not really ours
talking with God to remember
to God's money and he said he spent on
your sin and he also used to say
264.
all you who believe
do not modify your charity for your
thoughts
if you do you would realize one who
spends his money all day to show off
why is this believing in God and the
last death
his Parable despite the useless love
covers with a thinner of Souls when
heavy rainfalls it gives it solid they
harvest nothing from the airport
or you who believe do not modify
yourself
so this charity has followed by helping
people's feelings
are like somebody who's being charged to
provide this division in God
some people are very excited about the
we help a lot of people they've been to
hospital
have Central organization but they don't
believe in that
all the works
because of our existence here we are
here not to get started
so charity must be a form of worship
in obedience to that
the money
and the parable of those who spend their
money is seeking God's pleasure
and through their own conventions
the truth we need your phone number
back to 265.
the parable of God to spend their money
seeking God's pleasure and through their
own objectives
the death of a garden on a high and deep
soil
when heavy rain forms it builds double
the cross if heavy rain is not available
you want good land you have to make sure
there is uh it is
not water supply
with any of your wish to own a garden of
bed parts and grapes with flowing
streams and all kinds of fruits then as
he gets old and his children are still
weak
the garden gets written with a holocaust
the dirty stuff got us express the
Revelation for you that you may reflect
again this is emphasizing that
when you help somebody you don't the
kids
267.
all you who believe
you shall spend eternity from the good
things you earn and from what we produce
for you from the Earth
will not take out the Imperial thereof
to give away
when you would not accept it for
yourself unless your eyes are closed
to realize that God is Rich Worthy is
so this defines for us
what to uh what are the things that come
for itself
give away all clothes that you don't
need anymore that's not
um we're actually looking for this
problem here
instead of throwing them away for
something
charity must be must be as good as the
things you have
foreign
Ty and the exalts you to commit evil
work
when God promises you forgiveness from
him and flesh and bless him God is done
he bestows wisdom upon whomever he will
and whoever is endowed with wisdom will
endowed to the great family
that is because those who possession are
the ones who take you
so what do we understand through this
whole section
in the adequate for charity
from among the best things you have
and you get seven thousand percent
repair
and you do it and forget it
you do it
you never bring it up again you don't
tell other people the recipients again
and as you see in the next verse 270 if
you keep it secret
and that
because there's a
implies that you believe in God you know
that God saw you
if you don't keep it secret you tell
people around you know you're showing
off you're reaping sometimes it'll be
long
by not keeping the secret let's see if
you're 70.
whatever charity you give
or a barrel you make God is putting away
you're making me find no help
if you declare your charity
they are still good
but if you conceive them and give them
secretly to the poor it would be better
for you and would remit more of your
sins
God is fully cognizant to everything you
do
so this is where I start with somebody
else to check over that they have any
questions in this section so far
foreign
no
keep it simple
match
but
sometimes
confidence
thank you
Stronger Yeah
procedure
he could never guide anyone God is the
only one who guides in accordance with
his will make sure you give away
is for your own good
hey Charity